<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
        Data processing policy

         \n 1. General
The BlogTour application processes and protects the personal data of registered and unregistered users who access our application.
By providing us with personal data, you consent to their processing in accordance with this policy.

         \n 2. Definitions
Personal data - any information relating to a directly or indirectly identified or identifiable natural person (subject of personal data).
Processing of personal data - the implementation of actions or a set of actions in relation to personal data, including the collection, recording, systematization, accumulation, storage, clarification, updating and modification, extraction, use, provision, access, blocking, deletion and destruction - both using and and without the use of automated data processing tools.
We may process your data in the ways listed for the purposes set out in Section 4 of this Policy.
Personal data operator - a state body, municipal body, legal entity or individual, independently or jointly with other persons organizing and (or) carrying out the processing of personal data, as well as determining the purposes of processing personal data, the composition of personal data to be processed, actions (operations) committed with personal data.

        \n 3. What data we process
You provide us with personal data when:
Register in the application;
Posting publications;
Your device automatically transmits technical data: date and time of access to the application, actions in the application, technical characteristics of the device, IP address, etc.
We process only general categories of personal data. We do not process biometric personal data and special categories of personal data.
This Service may contain links to other websites. If you click on a third party link, you will be redirected to this site.
External sites are not controlled by this application. Therefore, I strongly recommend that you read the Privacy Policy of these resources.
The Application does not control and is not responsible for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party resources or Services.

         \n 4. Purposes of personal data processing
We process the personal data of users of the BlogTour app in the following ways:
Purposes of processing Data we may process (if applicable)
Allowing you to post, comment and rate posts, create a profile.
Prevention and suppression of violations of the law.
Fulfillment of obligations stipulated by law (for example, tax reporting, responding to requests from government agencies)
Providing answers to your requests: (Last name, first name, patronymic, phone number, e-mail address).

         \n 5. Legal basis for processing
We process your personal data:
With your consent.
You consent to the processing of your personal data upon registration and each time you enter the application, as well as in the process of using the BlogTour application.
You consent for 1 year from the date of deletion of your profile from the BlogTour service or, if you are an unregistered user, from the date of achievement of the purpose of processing personal data.
To fulfill our obligations under the law.

         \n 6. Information for children
Another part of our priority is to add child protection when using the Internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate and/or monitor and direct their online activities.
BlogTour does not knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13.
If you believe that your child has provided this type of information on our App, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best to promptly remove such information from our records.

         \n 7. Changes to this Privacy Policy
I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you are encouraged to review this page periodically for any changes.
This policy is valid from 03/10/2023

         \n 8. Storage of personal data
For data storage we use services: Google Play, Google Analytics for Firebase
We store your data in accordance with the data processing periods necessary to achieve the processing purposes specified in Section 4 of this Policy.

        \n 9. Terms of data processing
We stop processing your personal data within the terms established by law:
upon achievement of the purposes of processing specified in section 4 of this Policy, or if there is no need to achieve them (unless there are other grounds for processing provided by law).
For example, in order to fulfill the duties assigned to us, to prevent and suppress violations of laws, our rules, to protect users from fraudulent and other unfair actions, as well as to provide responses to requests, we must process data within the periods determined in accordance with the law (procedural , tax, civil, accounting, etc.).
We will also stop processing your data:
upon detection of unlawful processing, if lawfulness cannot be ensured;
when deleting an application.
After the expiration of the established deadlines, we automatically delete the data from the information systems. If the data is processed without the use of automatic processing tools (for example, paper applications), we destroy such material media.


         \n 10. Contact us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at: mobile.product.app@gmail.com
    </string>
</resources>