<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms_of_yandex">
       1. General Provisions

\n 1.1. YANDEX LLC (hereinafter referred to as Yandex) offers an Internet user (hereinafter referred to as the User) to use the Yandex.Maps service available at: https://maps.yandex.ru (hereinafter referred to as the Service).

\n 1.2. These Terms constitute an addition to the User Agreement for Yandex Services regarding the procedure for using the Service. In everything that is not provided for by these Terms, the relationship between Yandex and the User in connection with the use of the Service is governed by the User Agreement for Yandex Services (https://yandex.ru/legal/rules), as well as the License to Use the Yandex Search Engine (https:/ /yandex.ru/legal/termsofuse), Privacy Policy (https://yandex.ru/legal/confidential).

\n 1.3. Starting to use the Service / its individual functions, the User is considered to have accepted these Terms, as well as the terms of all the above documents, in full, without any reservations or exceptions. If the User disagrees with any of the provisions of these documents, the User is not entitled to use the Service.

\n 1.4. These Terms may be changed by Yandex without any special notice, the new version of the Terms shall enter into force from the moment it is posted on the Internet at the address specified in this paragraph, unless otherwise provided by the new version of the Terms. The current version of the Terms is always located on the page at: https://yandex.ru/legal/maps_termsofuse.

\n 1.5. If Yandex has made any changes to these Terms, in the manner provided for in clause 1.4. of these Terms, with which the User does not agree, he is obliged to stop using the Service.

\n 1.6. The Service offers the User the possibility of free access to up-to-date cartographic and other reference information. All currently existing functions of the Service, as well as any development and / or addition of new ones, are subject to these Terms.

\n 1.7. By using the Service, the User agrees to receive informational and advertising messages. The User has the right to refuse to receive advertising messages by using the corresponding functionality of the Service or by following the instructions specified in the received advertising message.
\n 2. Use of the Service. Separate functions of the Service
\n 2.1. The Service provides the User with the functionality to independently and at their choice add user information to the cards, including signs, labels, text signatures, messages, etc. (hereinafter referred to as "User Objects"). The application of User objects does not modify the original data and is allowed solely for the convenience of using the Service by the User. The User has the right to create, save, and place links to User Objects in free access on the Internet. Links to User Objects may also be distributed by other users of the Service.

\n 2.2. The User independently and entirely bears all the risks and responsibility for choosing the location of the User Objects, compliance with the law, content, completeness, correctness and reliability of the description of the added User Objects. Yandex does not bear any responsibility for the designation and description of any User Object, does not confirm or refute the compliance with the law, the correctness and reliability of the description of any User Object. Yandex reserves the right, without warning and at its own discretion, to remove any User Object or set of User Objects if the information contained in its description contradicts the laws of the Russian Federation, contains profanity, and also in other cases when the designation and/or description of the User Objects and/or distributing a link to User Objects violates these Terms, the terms of use of other Yandex services, or the provisions of the documents specified in clause 1.2. of these Terms, as well as in order to protect the interests of Yandex, service users, and other third parties.

\n 2.3. The service provides the user with the functionality to receive the card code in the state at the time of receipt of the code, for insertion into their website, blog, mobile application. This function can be used by the User only within the framework of websites or mobile applications available for free open use by an unlimited number of people. The function cannot be used for projects that require payment or otherwise restrict access to them by third parties. The need to register is not considered a restriction of access under this paragraph.

\n 2.4. The Service provides the User with the functionality of automatically building routes on maps indicating the route option from the point of departure to the point of destination specified by the User (hereinafter referred to as the "Route"). Building Routes does not modify the original data and is allowed solely for the convenience of using the Service by the User.

The User independently and entirely bears all risks and responsibility for choosing the Route and following the selected Route. Yandex does not guarantee the correctness, optimality, relevance and/or compliance of the Routes with traffic rules and is not responsible for the Users choice of the Route and the consequences of following it. The User must take all measures of care and discretion before choosing a Route and during its use.

\n 2.5. The Service may contain information about the current level of traffic congestion, a short-term congestion forecast, as well as information about the average traffic congestion during the day (hereinafter referred to as the Yandex.Traffic Service).

The information available in the Yandex.Traffic Service was obtained based on the analysis of anonymized data and is for reference only.

The color display of the road congestion level used in the Service is not an indication of the status of the road, the possibility of its free use, actual operation and passability, and is only an indicator of the approximate degree of its congestion in the current period of time (green - free, yellow - medium congestion, red - high congestion).

\n 2.6. The Service may provide the User with the functionality to search and view information about the movement of public transport (hereinafter referred to as the "Transport Mode") on a map of a certain area. The information displayed when using the "Transport" Mode is provided by the partners of the Service and / or obtained from open public sources and is for reference only, Yandex is not responsible for the accuracy, relevance and reliability of the information provided, including public transport routes and directions, transport schedules, as well as finding public transport at a certain point on the map.

\n 2.7. The Service uses intellectual property objects, the rights to which belong to the respective copyright holders, as well as information provided by its owners. A complete list of copyright holders and information owners is listed in clause 5 of these Terms.

\n 2.8. The Service may provide the User with the opportunity to make a booking for the services of an organization, subject to the availability of a booking form for the relevant organization in the Service.

The booking is made by the User filling out the booking form and specifying the necessary information.

By filling out and sending the booking form, the User agrees to the processing of the data specified in the form by Yandex under the terms of the Privacy Policy (https://yandex.ru/legal/confidential), as well as to the transfer of data to the organization in respect of whose services the booking is requested, for the purpose of pre-booking services and feedback on booking and provision of services to the User, as well as for the purpose of feedback from the organization with the User on the provision of services / sale of goods.

\n 2.9. The user has the opportunity to book services provided by the organization using the Yclients service provided by the Service partner on the terms published at: https://www.yclients.com/info/user-agreement. When filling out the booking form and making a booking using it, the User agrees to send the data specified in the form to LLC "WAYCLAIENTS" (OGRN: 5157746100716), as well as representatives of the organization in respect of whose services the booking is requested, for the purpose of pre-booking services and making feedback on planning and provision of services to the User.

\n 2.10. The Service may provide the User with the opportunity to entrust Yandex with the transfer of funds in favor of the State Public Institution of the City of Moscow "Administrator of the Moscow Parking Space" in payment for placing the User\'s vehicle on flat objects and on the territory of paid city parking lots in Moscow in accordance with the Decrees of the Government of Moscow dated 05/17/2013 No. 289-PP "On the organization of paid urban parking in the city of Moscow" and dated 09/16/2014 No. 533-PP "On paid urban flat parking of a closed type in the city of Moscow" and in the manner established by them (hereinafter referred to as the Order). The Order shall be executed by Yandex, if technically possible, on behalf of the User and at his expense. The amount of money required to pay for the placement of the User\'s vehicle at flat sites and paid city parking areas in Moscow, and the amount of the Yandex commission for executing the Order, are communicated to the User in the Service interface. In order to fulfill the instructions specified in this paragraph, Yandex has the right to engage third parties. For the avoidance of doubt, Yandex does not fulfill the User\'s instruction to return unused funds from the parking account, the return of funds is carried out directly by GKU "AMPP".

\n 2.11. In cases provided for by applicable law, when funds are collected from the User, or when they are returned, a cash receipt is sent to the e-mail address created during registration in Yandex ID (https://passport.yandex.ru) of the account under which the User was authorized at the time of payment or to the subscriber number specified by the User when using the services of Yandex (its affiliates).
\n 3. Using the Yandex.Business function
\n 3.1. The Service provides the User with the functionality to post, view and search for information about organizations located at the addresses displayed in the Service (hereinafter referred to as Yandex.Business), including information about the address, name, contact information, mode of operation, information about the services provided / goods sold and user reviews. The use of Yandex.Business and its sections is subject to the Terms of Use of the Yandex.Business service published at: https://yandex.ru/legal/clients_termsofuse.

The functionality of Yandex.Business may vary depending on the region/country of the User\'s location.

\n 3.2.- 3.9. No longer valid (clauses in the new edition are published at the address specified in clause 3.1. of the Terms).
\n 4. Other provisions
\n 4.1. Yandex does not guarantee the safety of information provided in the Service (including User objects and information of the Yandex.Business service, Yandex.Traffic, etc.) to any extent and/or for any period of time, including in the event of data changes in connection with the development or change of the Service.

\n 4.2. Information from the Service may be used by Yandex in other Yandex services and applications, as well as in advertising or marketing materials posted on Yandex resources on the Internet to draw the attention of other users to the content of the Service, to the Service as a whole, or to other Yandex applications and services, goods , works and services of third parties, both with an indication of the author of the information (the name (pseudonym) of the User, which he indicated during registration or in the settings of his data in the corresponding section of the Service), and without it, without the need to obtaining the User\
        \'s special permission and without payment of royalties, with the right of Yandex to grant the rights to use the information to third parties for use in the specified advertising or marketing materials. At the same time, the User acknowledges and agrees that Yandex is not obliged to view the information posted by the Users in the Service. If the User is not entitled to grant Yandex the right to use any information in this way, he is obliged to refrain from posting such information.

\n 4.3. If the settings of the User\'s operating system allow the Service to receive information about the User\'s location, Yandex may receive the specified information and transfer it to the organization feedback collection service provided by a Yandex affiliate located in Russia or another country. The specified information can be used to send push notifications to the User in the Service and/or in other services of Yandex and its affiliates used by the User, if they allow sending push notifications, with a request to leave a review about an organization about which the User may have an opinion based on his personal experience. In order not to receive appropriate push notifications based on information about the User\'s location received by the Service, the User may prohibit the Service from receiving information about the User\'s location in the settings of the User\'s operating system or prohibit sending push notifications in the Service and other Yandex services or Yandex affiliates used by the User.

\n 4.4. Yandex reserves the right, at its discretion, to restrict the User\'s access to the Service (or to certain functions of the Service, if technologically possible) using his account or to completely block the User\'s account in case of repeated violation of these Terms, or to take other measures against the User in order to compliance with the requirements of the law or the rights and legitimate interests of third parties.

\n 4.5. Using the Service, the User can report the inaccuracy of the information posted in the Service (incorrect name, location on the map, irrelevance of the data, the need to delete the object), indicating the relevant information in a special form of communication of the Service. The content of the message sent by the User when using this functionality is publicly available and is openly posted in the Yandex.People\'s Map service (https://n.maps.yandex.ru) in order to obtain an assessment of the registered users of such a service regarding the reliability and relevance of the information provided. . By sending a message, the User agrees to the publication of the message form he filled out. The User undertakes not to indicate in the message information that is classified by the legislation of the Russian Federation as information of limited access, including personal data, personal data of third parties, as well as information whose distribution is prohibited.
\n 4.6. Any information used in the Service is intended solely for personal non-commercial use. At the same time, any copying of the Data, their reproduction, processing, distribution, making available to the public (publication) on the Internet, any use in the media and / or for commercial purposes without the prior written permission of the copyright holder is prohibited, except as expressly provided for by the functional service capabilities, these Terms, the terms of use of other Yandex services, or the documents specified in clause 1.2. of these Terms.

\n 4.7. The information provided in the Service is for reference only. Yandex does not guarantee that the Service, the quality of any product, service, information obtained using the Service meets / will meet the User\'s requirements, and that the functions of the Service will be provided continuously, quickly, reliably and without errors.

Yandex does not guarantee the accuracy, relevance, completeness, or reliability of the information that can be obtained using the Service. The information of the Service is not intended to be used for any purpose or in any capacity (for example, to establish and / or confirm any facts, as evidence when making legally significant decisions, to provide information and conduct accurate calculations, research, obtaining accurate coordinates and information about official names, determining a position regarding the status of objects or territories, etc.).

\n 5. Information about copyright holders and information owners:
The list of copyright holders and owners of the information used can be found at: https://yandex.ru/legal/right_holders
    </string>
</resources>